A Guide to the Chesapeake Western Railway Company Records, 1928-1982: SC 0154
Special Collections, Carrier Library, James Madison University
Chesapeake Western Railway Company Records,
1928-1982
Special Collections, James Madison University
Chesapeake Western Railway Company
SC 0154
23.89 cubic feet; 34 boxes, 1 rolled storage container
The Chespeake Western Railway Company Records, 1928-1982, are comprised of 23.89 cubic feet of records pertaining to the administrative and business activities of a small Shenandoah Valley railroad through the period of America's Great Depression and up to the CW's eventual acquisition by the Norfolk Southern Railway Corporation.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection is open to research. Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection. Please contact Research Services staff before visiting the James Madison University Special Collections Library to use this collection.
Acquisition Information
D.A. Brown, II Superintendent, VA Division of Norfolk Southern in Roanoke gave permission in April 1997 for JMU professors Raymond Hiser and Clarence Geier from the History and Anthropology Departments respectively to salvage records from the CW building on Chesapeake Drive in Harrisonburg, Virginia which suffered a five-alarm fire at the site on July 28, 1982. After the fire, operating records remained in the building in disarray on the floor and suffered damage by fire or water or both. Following their initial cleaning and inventory by students in History and Anthropology, the materials were transferred to Carrier Library in February 1998.
Provenance
Records represent the day to day business operation of the Chesapeake Western Railway Company through 1982. After a fire that year, records were left in the CW building on Chesapeake Drive in Harrisonburg, Virginia, and remained in that facility until 1997.
Administrative History
The origins of the Chesapeake Western Railway Company date back at least to 1871, when the Washington, Cincinnati & St. Louis Railroad was chartered in Virginia as a narrow-gauge railroad to run from Washington, D.C., through Elkton, Harrisonburg, and Bridgewater, Virginia to Cincinnati, Ohio. Virginians bought stock in the coporation, including many people in Rockingham County; rights of way were purchased and railbed grading began. Like similar ventures of the time, the goals of the company never bore fruit, and work halted in 1874.
In 1892, a group of promoters including Jedediah Hotchkiss incorporated to build a railway to carry coal from West Virginia mines to Gloucester Point, Virginia. Initially called the Chesapeake, Shendun, and Western Railroad, the name was quickly changed to Chesapeake & Western Railroad. Using part of the old WC&StL right-of-way, and with $150,000 from the city of Harrisonburg to ensure that the railroad would pass through it, a 26-mile single-track, standard-gauge line was completed from Elkton to Bridgewater and began operating on March 23, 1896. In the next few years, substantial C&W stock was purchased by New York investor Thomas Stokes, who hoped to develop the coal mines in western Rockingham County but became mired in financial difficulties. His brother, W.E.D Stokes, purchased control of the C&W and also organized a new railroad, the Tidewater and West Virginia, in 1900. The Tidewater changed its name in 1901 to the Chesapeake Western Railway, leased the CW line for 99 years, and in 1902 completed 13 miles of rail from Bridgewater to the new town of Stokesville in North River Gap. Trains carried passengers as well as freight between Elkton and Stokesville. Plans were drawn up to continue the line into West Virginia but were not implemented.
For just over a decade, Stokesville boomed as timber, tanbark, and to a much more limited extent, coal, in the area were exploited. Stokes operated the CW with offices in Harrisonburg until his death in 1926. His estate continued to operate the railway until 1938. In 1928, thi line from Mount Solon to North River Gap was abandoned for financial reasons. In 1933, the nine miles from Bridgewater to Mount Solon were also dropped. When the Stokes' heirs put the CW up for sale in 1938, Don W. Thomas, a former Norfolk & Western Railroad employee who had been the general manager of the CW since 1926, fought a bid from Japanese scrap metal buyers and bought the line. In 1943, Thomas also bought the Baltimore & Ohio's Valley Road of Virginia line which rean between Harrisonburg and Lexington. The line south of Staunton was taken up and sold for scrap, but the road between Harrisonburg and Staunton was improved and became an important link in the CW system because of the connection with the Chesapeake & Ohio Railroad at Staunton. The CW linked with the Norfolk & Western at Elkton.
In 1954, the Norfolk & Western Railroad purchased CW, but the name was retained and was oeprated as a separate corporation. By about 1980, however, little or no rolling stock carried the CW logo any longer. Norfolk & Western and the Southern Railway Company merged as Norfolk Southern Corporation on June 1, 1982. Not long after that merger, a five-alarm fire burned the CW office located at Chesapeake Drive in Harrisonburg on July 28, 1982, and company offices and operations were eventually absorbed by the NS. Five miles of track east of Bridgewater were removed in 1988. The CW under the control of NS serves as the Harrisonburg area's poultry feed supplier passing through the campus of James Madison University daily.
Scope and Content
The Chesapeake Western Railway Company Records, 1928-1982, consist of 23.89 cubic feet of business records pertaining to the employees, assets, and business transactions of the company. The collection is topically arranged in seven series with the largest series first; then further arranged chronologically. Series consist of Personnel Records, Reports, Account Books, Correspondence, Blueprints and Schematics, Publications, and Miscellaneous Documents.
Arrangement
The collection is arranged in seven series with the largest first; then further arranged chronologically:
Series 1: Personnel Records, 1929-1982
Series 2: Reports, 1953-1981
Series 3: Account Books, 1932-1974
Series 4: Correspondence, 1976-1979
Series 5: Miscellaneous Documents, 1928-1976
Series 6: Publications, 1963-1977
Series 7: Blueprints and Schematics, 1951-1979
Bibliography
Cooper, Mason Y. Norfolk and Western's Shenandoah Line. Forest, Virginia: Norfolk and Western Historical Society, Inc., 1998.
Cooper, Mason Y. Norfolk and Western's Shenandoah Line. Forest, Virginia: Norfolk and Western Historical Society, Inc., 1998.
Hawkins, Leighman. "The Shortline Railroads of Virginia." Virginia and the Virginia County, January 1951.
Murray, Michael S. "Rails Through Rockingham County: The Chesapeake Western Story." Railpace Newsmagazine, January 1985.
"Norfolk and Western to buy Chesapeake Western." Daily News-Record, July 29, 1954.
Price, Charles Grattan Jr. The Crooked and the Weedy: A History of Virginia's Chesapeake Western Railway. Harrisonburg, Virginia: Don Mills, Inc., 1992.
Thompson, Tommy. "Shortline." Daily News-Record, April 3, 1971.
Index Terms
Subjects:
Stokes, W. E. D; Chesapeake and Western Railroad Company; Norfolk Southern Corporation; Railroads -- Southern States -- History -- Sources; Railroads -- Virginia -- History -- Sources; Coal -- Transportation -- Southern States -- Sources; Bark -- Transportation -- Southern States -- Sources; Timber -- Transportation -- Southern States -- Sources; Poultry -- Feeding and feeds -- Transportation -- Southern States -- Sources; Elkton (Va.) -- History -- Sources; Harrisonburg (Va.) -- History -- Sources; Bridgewater (Va.) -- History -- Sources; Mt. Solon (Va.) -- History -- Sources; Stokesville (Va.) -- History -- Sources; Rockingham County (Va.) -- Industries -- Sources; Augusta County (Va.) -- Industries -- Sources; Virginia -- Economic conditions -- History -- Sources; Virginia -- Industries -- History -- Sources; Shenandoah River Valley (Va. and W. Va.) -- Transportation -- History -- Sources
- Series 1: Personnel Records, 1929-1982
  Scope and Content
  Series 1: Personnel Records, 1929-1982, includes payrolls and time sheets with names of employees, occupations, hours, rates, payments, and dates of employment. Also included in this series are Railroad Retirement Board forms primarily from 1930 to 1973, containing employee biographical and genealogical information.
  - Payroll, 1929 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Payroll, 1930 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Payroll, 1931 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Payroll, 1932 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Payroll, 1933 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Payroll, 1934 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Payroll, 1935 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Payroll, 1936 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Payroll, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Payroll, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Payroll, 1939 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Payroll, 1940 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Time reports, January-April 1941 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Time reports, May-August 1941 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Time reports, September-December 1941 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Time reports, January-April 1942 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Time reports, May-August 1942 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Time reports, September-December 1942 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Time reports, January-March 1944 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Time reports, April-June 1944 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Time reports, July-September 1944 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Time reports, October-December 1944 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Time reports, January-March 1945 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Time reports, April 1945 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Time reports, May-June 1945 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Time reports, July-September 1945 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Time reports, October-December 1945 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Time reports, January-April 1947 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Time reports, May-August 1947 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Time reports, September-December 1947 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Payroll and timesheets, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Payroll and timesheets (folder 1 of 2), January 1978 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Payroll and timesheets (folder 2 of 2), January 1978 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Payroll and timesheets (folder 1 of 3), February 1978 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Payroll and timesheets (folder 2 of 3), February 1978 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Payroll and timesheets (folder 3 of 3), February 1978 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Payroll and timesheets (folder 1 of 2), March 1978 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Payroll and timesheets (folder 2 of 2), March 1978 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Payroll and timesheets (folder 1 of 2), April 1978 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Payroll and timesheets (folder 2 of 2), April 1978 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Payroll and timesheets (folder 1 of 3), May 1978 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Payroll and timesheets (folder 2 of 3), May 1978 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Payroll and timesheets (folder 3 of 3), May 1978 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Payroll and timesheets (folder 1 of 2), June 1978 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Payroll and timesheets (folder 2 of 2), June 1978 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Payroll and timesheets (folder 1 of 3), July 1978 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Payroll and timesheets (folder 2 of 3), July 1978 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Payroll and timesheets (folder 3 of 3), July 1978 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Payroll and timesheets (folder 1 of 3), August 1978 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Payroll and timesheets (folder 2 of 3), August 1978 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Payroll and timesheets (folder 3 of 3), August 1978 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Payroll and timesheets (folder 1 of 2), September 1978 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Payroll and timesheets (folder 2 of 2), September 1978 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Payroll and timesheets (folder 1 of 2), October 1978 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Payroll and timesheets (folder 2 of 2), October 1978 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Payroll and timesheets (folder 1 of 2), November 1978 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Payroll and timesheets (folder 2 of 2), November 1978 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Payroll and timesheets (folder 1 of 2), December 1978 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Payroll and timesheets (folder 2 of 2), December 1978 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Payroll and timesheets (folder 1 of 2), January 1979 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Payroll and timesheets (folder 2 of 2), January 1979 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Payroll and timesheets (folder 1 of 2), February 1979 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Payroll and timesheets (folder 2 of 2), February 1979 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Payroll and timesheets (folder 1 of 3), March 1979 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Payroll and timesheets (folder 2 of 3), March 1979 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Payroll and timesheets (folder 3 of 3), March 1979 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Payroll and timesheets (folder 1 of 2), April 1979 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Payroll and timesheets (folder 2 of 2), April 1979 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Payroll and timesheets (folder 1 of 3), May 1979 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Payroll and timesheets (folder 2 of 3), May 1979 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Payroll and timesheets (folder 3 of 3), May 1979 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Payroll and timesheets (folder 1 of 2), June 1979 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Payroll and timesheets (folder 2 of 2), June 1979 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Payroll and timesheets (folder 1 of 2), July 1979 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Payroll and timesheets (folder 2 of 2), July 1979 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Payroll and timesheets (folder 1 of 2), August 1979 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Payroll and timesheets (folder 2 of 2), August 1979 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Payroll and timesheets (folder 1 of 2), September 1979 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Payroll and timesheets (folder 2 of 2), September 1979 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Payroll and timesheets (folder 1 of 2), October 1979 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Payroll and timesheets (folder 2 of 2), October 1979 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Payroll and timesheets (folder 1 of 2), November 1979 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Payroll and timesheets (folder 2 of 2), November 1979 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Payroll and timesheets (folder 1 of 2), December 1979 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Payroll and timesheets (folder 2 of 2), December 1979 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Payroll and timesheets (folder 1 of 2), January 1980 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Payroll and timesheets (folder 2 of 2), January 1980 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Payroll and timesheets (folder 1 of 2), February 1980 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Payroll and timesheets (folder 2 of 2), February 1980 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Payroll and timesheets (folder 1 of 2), March 1980 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Payroll and timesheets (folder 2 of 2), March 1980 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Payroll and timesheets (folder 1 of 2), April 1980 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Payroll and timesheets (folder 2 of 2), April 1980 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Payroll and timesheets (folder 1 of 2), May 1980 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Payroll and timesheets (folder 2 of 2), May 1980 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Payroll and timesheets (folder 1 of 2), June 1980 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Payroll and timesheets (folder 2 of 2), June 1980 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Payroll and timesheets (folder 1 of 2), July 1980 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Payroll and timesheets (folder 2 of 2), July 1980 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Payroll and timesheets (folder 1 of 2), August 1980 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Payroll and timesheets (folder 2 of 2), August 1980 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Payroll and timesheets (folder 1 of 2), September 1980 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Payroll and timesheets (folder 2 of 2), September 1980 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Payroll and timesheets (folder 1 of 2), October 1980 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Payroll and timesheets (folder 2 of 2), October 1980 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Payroll and timesheets (folder 1 of 2), November 1980 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Payroll and timesheets (folder 2 of 2), November 1980 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Payroll and timesheets (folder 1 of 2), December 1980 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Payroll and timesheets (folder 2 of 2), December 1980 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Payroll and timesheets (folder 1 of 2), January 1981 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Payroll and timesheets (folder 2 of 2), January 1981 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Payroll and timesheets (folder 1 of 2), February 1981 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Payroll and timesheets (folder 2 of 2), February 1981 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Payroll and timesheets (folder 1 of 2), March 1981 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Payroll and timesheets (folder 2 of 2), March 1981 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Payroll and timesheets (folder 1 of 2), April 1981 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Payroll and timesheets (folder 2 of 2), April 1981 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Payroll and timesheets (folder 1 of 2), May 1981 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Payroll and timesheets (folder 2 of 2), May 1981 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Payroll and timesheets (folder 1 of 2), June 1981 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Payroll and timesheets (folder 2 of 2), June 1981 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Payroll and timesheets (folder 1 of 2), July 1981 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Payroll and timesheets (folder 2 of 2), July 1981 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Payroll and timesheets (folder 1 of 2), August 1981 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Payroll and timesheets (folder 2 of 2), August 1981 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Payroll and timesheets (folder 1 of 2), September 1981 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Payroll and timesheets (folder 2 of 2), September 1981 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Payroll and timesheets (folder 1 of 2), October 1981 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Payroll and timesheets (folder 2 of 2), October 1981 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Payroll and timesheets (folder 1 of 2), November 1981 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Payroll and timesheets (folder 2 of 2), November 1981 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Payroll and timesheets (folder 1 of 2), December 1981 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Payroll and timesheets (folder 2 of 2), December 1981 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Payroll and timesheets (folder 1 of 2), January 1982 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Payroll and timesheets (folder 2 of 2), January 1982 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Payroll and timesheets (folder 1 of 2), February 1982 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Payroll and timesheets (folder 2 of 2), February 1982 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Payroll and timesheets (folder 1 of 2), March 1982 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Payroll and timesheets (folder 2 of 2), March 1982 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Payroll and timesheets (folder 1 of 2), April 1982 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Payroll and timesheets (folder 2 of 2), April 1982 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Payroll and timesheets (folder 1 of 2), May 1982 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Payroll and timesheets (folder 2 of 2), May 1982 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Payroll and timesheets (folder 1 of 2), June 1982 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Payroll and timesheets (folder 2 of 2), June 1982 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Railroad Retirement Board, Forms, 1930s-1941 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Railroad Retirement Board, Employee Personnel Records, 1930s-1943 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Railroad Retirement Board, Employee Personnel Records, 1941-1973 (Box 22, Folder 7)
- Series 2: Reports, 1953-1981
  Series 2: Reports, 1953-1981, primarily is comprised of Dispatcher and Conductor reports, with information about specific trains, routes, departure times, distances and engine numbers. Dispatchers' Record of Movement of Trains, 1973-1979, and Time Return and Delay Reports, 1975-1981, list information such as: engineers' names, train departure times, type of service, etc. Conductor Car Records and tonnage Reports include engine number, weight of trains, cargo, as well as identification of conductors and engineers on each train. Entries for Shipping logs, 1970-1977; Traffic Analyses and other shipping records, 1973-1981, are followed by Per Diem/Mileage and Transfer Books, 1953-1970, which appear to be freight and transfer records written in abbreviated code and organized alphabetically by company name.
  - Dispatcher's Record of Movement of Trains, Vol. 2, January-April 1973 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Dispatcher's Record of Movement of Trains, Vol. 2, May-August 1973 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Dispatcher's Record of Movement of Trains, Vol. 2, September-December 1973 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Dispatcher's Record of Movement of Trains, Vol. 2, January-April 1974 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Dispatcher's Record of Movement of Trains, Vol. 2, May-July 1974 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Dispatcher's Record of Movement of Trains, Vol. 2, August-October 1974 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Dispatcher's Record of Movement of Trains, Vol. 2, November-December 1974 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Dispatcher's Record of Movement of Trains, Vol. 2, January-April 1975 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Dispatcher's Record of Movement of Trains, Vol. 2, May-August 1975 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Dispatcher's Record of Movement of Trains, Vol. 2, September-December 1975 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Dispatcher's Record of Movement of Trains, Vol. 3, January-April 1976 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Dispatcher's Record of Movement of Trains, Vol. 3, May-August 1976 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Dispatcher's Record of Movement of Trains, Vol. 3, September-December 1976 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Dispatcher's Record of Movement of Trains, Vol. 3, January-June 1977 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Dispatcher's Record of Movement of Trains, Vol. 3, July-December 1977 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Dispatcher's Record of Movement of Trains, Vol. 3, January-March 1978 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Dispatcher's Record of Movement of Trains, Vol. 3, April-June 1978 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - Dispatcher's Record of Movement of Trains, Vol. 3, July-October 1978 (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - Dispatcher's Record of Movement of Trains, Vol. 3, November-December 1978 (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - Dispatcher's Record of Movement of Trains, Vol. 3, January-June 1979 (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - Dispatcher's Record of Movement of Trains, Vol. 3, July-December 1979 (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - Time Return & Delay Reports, January 1975 (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - Time Return & Delay Reports, February 1975 (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - Time Return & Delay Reports, March 1975 (Box 18, Folder 33)
  - Time Return & Delay Reports, April 1975 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Time Return & Delay Reports, May 1975 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Time Return & Delay Reports, June 1975 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Time Return & Delay Reports, July 1975 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Time Return & Delay Reports, August 1975 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Time Return & Delay Reports, September 1975 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Time Return & Delay Reports, October 1975 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Time Return & Delay Reports, November 1975 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Time Return & Delay Reports, December 1975 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Time Return & Delay Reports, January 1976 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Time Return & Delay Reports, February 1976 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Time Return & Delay Reports, March 1976 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Time Return & Delay Reports, April 1976 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Time Return & Delay Reports, May 1976 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Time Return & Delay Reports, June 1976 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Time Return & Delay Reports, July 1976 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Time Return & Delay Reports, August 1976 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Time Return & Delay Reports, September 1976 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Time Return & Delay Reports, October 1976 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Time Return & Delay Reports, November 1976 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Time Return & Delay Reports, December 1976 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Time Return & Delay Reports, January 1977 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Time Return & Delay Reports, February 1977 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Time Return & Delay Reports, March 1977 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Time Return & Delay Reports, April 1977 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Time Return & Delay Reports, May 1977 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - Time Return & Delay Reports, June 1977 (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - Time Return & Delay Reports, July 1977 (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - Time Return & Delay Reports, August 1977 (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - Time Return & Delay Reports, September 1977 (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - Time Return & Delay Reports, October 1977 (Box 19, Folder 31)
  - Time Return & Delay Reports, November 1977 (Box 19, Folder 32)
  - Time Return & Delay Reports, December 1977 (Box 19, Folder 33)